Viewers all over the world, whatever medium you are using to view us,
you are with us and we are with you.
This is the moment of salvation,
moment of healing,
moment of deliverance,
moment of breakthrough.
Hallelujah!
Remember, at this moment, you have been forgiven of all your sins
and if the Son forgives you, you are delivered.
Say to yourself, "If the Son forgives me, I'm delivered".
Be delivered in the name of Jesus!
Whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself -
these are the instruments satan uses to connect us to himself:
sickness, hardship, depression - whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself,
open you lips, by the power of resurrection -
that good health that has been taken from you,
that promotion that has been taken from you,
your destined position that has been taken from you,
your destined marriage that has been taken from you,
be restored, in the name of Jesus!
By the power of resurrection, be restored, in the name of Jesus!
Viewers all over the world, I command every sick organ, be it your kidneys, liver, blood, bones, fluids
be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Power of the Holy Ghost!
Holy Ghost!
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, begin to disconnect your business from anything that has to do with demons, satan.
Disconnect your business from failure.
Disconnect your business from backwardness..
Disconnect your marriage from backwardness, setback.
Give thanks to God.
Yes.
Jesus has made you whole; give thanks to Him.
He made you fit for healing, deliverance, blessing.
He made you fit for God Almighty.
Rejoice!
Happy Easter!